jinPlayer is high performance player. It supports almost all format local file and streaming (HLS, HTTP, RTSP). 
1. Performance is very good.
2. Animation UI is comfortable.
3. It can playback 1080P HEVC file realtime.
4. The Security box protect your persoaal media file.
5. Zoom video help you see the special pare clearly.
6. The professional file properties show more detail info.

Contact: jinplayer@qq.com

